BRAC Additional Records 5735
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Workmen's Compensation and Unemployment Insurance (States), 1979 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- United States Congress - Interstate Commerce Proposed Amendments (Slurry Pipelines), 1961-1977 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  April 1, 1961-January 1977
- United States Congress - Proposed Amendments to the Interstate Commerce Act, 1963-1969 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  May 1, 1963-March 1969
- Acts of Congress - Amendments to the Interstate Commerce Act, 1962-1964 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  S. 1061 H.R. 4700 and S. 3243 H.R. 11583 to amend the Interstate Commerce Act to exempt the railroads from minimum rate regulations of movement of agriculture and bulk commodities, etcetera.
- Taft-Hartley Act (General), 1950 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  November 1950. Includes Bound Materials.
- Taft-Hartley Acts - Amendments, 1954-1966 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  March 1954-1966
- Universal Military Training - Vietnam Era Veteran Readjustment Act of 1974 and General, 1973-1977 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  January 1973-January 1977
- United States Congress - Welfare and Pension Funds Disclosure Legislation, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  January 1, 1974-July 1975
- Surface Transportation Committee (Railroads), 1961-1975 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  July 1, 1961-April 1975
- Surface Transportation Committee (Airlines), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  September 16, 1959
- Landrum-Griffin Reporting and Disclosure Act, 1962-1979 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  December 1, 1962-March 1979
- Civil Rights Act - Henry Craighead et al - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  June 1978
- AMTRAK - Old Papers, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  July 1971
- United States Congress - Rail Passenger Service Act of 1970 (Railpax), 1973-1978 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- AMTRAK, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  October 1979. Includes Bound Materials.
- Occupational Safety and Health Act of 1970, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  May 1979
- Rolling Stock Utilization and Financing Act of 1972, 1972-1978 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  1972-March 1978
- United States Congress - National Mass Transportation Assistance Act of 1974, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- United States Congress - Employee Retirement Income Security Act of 1974 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  1974-April 1977
- United States Congress - Railroad Revitalization and Regulatory Act of 1975, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  July 1976
- Railroad Revitalization and Regulatory Reform Act of 1976 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Legislative Files (General), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  February 1972
- State Legislation - Right to Work Laws (Various States), 1972-1979 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  January 1, 1972-September 1979
- State Legislation - Illinois Regional Transportation Authority, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  January-September 1975
- State Legislation - Illinois, 1974-1978 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  February 1974-March 1978
- State Legislation - Indiana, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  January-September 1974
- State Legislation - Kentucky, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- State Legislation - New Jersey, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  July 1974
- State Legislation - New Mexico, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  February 1974
- State Legislation - New York, 1976-1979 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  1976-December 1979
- State Legislation - Ohio, 1973-1979 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  August 1973-November 1979
- State Legislation - Texas, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  January-February 1977
- State Legislation - Virginia, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- State Legislation - Washington, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  January-April 1978
- State Legislation - West Virginia, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  January-May 1979
- Credentials - Grand Lodge Officers, 1947-1971 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  1947-September 1971
- Credentials - Special Organizers, 1961-1964 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  January 1, 1961-November 1964
- Credentials - Regional and General Representatives, Grand Lodge Organizer, Field Representative, 1960-1972 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  1960- December 1972
- National Railroad Adjustment Board - Obligation of Funds (Salaries), 1968-1975 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  January 1, 1968-October 1975
- National Railroad Adjustment Board - Awards - Printing Invoices and Prices, 1961-1970 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  January 1, 1961-June 1970
- Grand Lodge Officers, 1972-1979 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  January 1, 1972-August 1979
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers, 1960-1976 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  January 1, 1960-July 1976
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (C.E. Carter), 1966-1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  1966-June 1970
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (Condo), 1970-1972 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (Cusumano), 1970 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  June 26, 1970
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (S. Costa), 1963-1970 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  1963-June 1970
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (D.S. Cooper), 1967-1971 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  1967-July 1971
- Grand Lodge Officers - Joe Condo (Organizer), 1974 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  January 22, 1974-March 1974
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (Thomas Fitzgibbons), 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  1968-July 1969
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (J.B. Gordon), 1967 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (D.K. Hoback), 1965-1971 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  1965-August 1971
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (F.A. Huici), 1964-1966 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  1964-December 1966
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (Hagad), 1970 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (K.F. Lassell), 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  1968-June 1970
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (L. Leroux), 1964-1969 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  1964-February 1969
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (F.T. Lynch), 1968-1972 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  1968-September1972
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (W.A. MacKay), 1961-1969 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  1961-May 1969
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (E.P. Matts), 1965-1970 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  1965-March 1970
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (A.W. McCauley), 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (F. E. McCarthy), 1958-1965 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  1958-February 1965
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (D. Lockhart), 1966-1971 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  1966-July 1971
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (W.A. Schults), 1970 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  July 1, 1970
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (Radice), 1970 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (F.D. Sheahan), 1966-1970 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  1966-August 1970
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (N.J. Trombetta), 1963-1972 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  1963-June 1972
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (Wilbur), 1970 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (Wilson), 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  1967-April 1968
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Representatives and Organizers (W.R. Williamson), 1964-1973 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  1964-March 1973
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of International Vice Presidents (General), 1975-1980 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  May 1975-1980
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of the Vice Presidents, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  1975-November 1976
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of the Vice President S.G. Bishop, 1972-1976 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  1972-September 1976
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Vice President C.S. Coleman, 1971-1977 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  1971-October 1977
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Vice President R.J. Devlin, 1969-1974 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  1969-March 1974
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of Vice President T. Fitzgibbon, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 36)
- International President Granlund, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 37)
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of International Vice President R.I. Kilroy, 1971-1975 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  1971-October 1975
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of International Vice President F.J.. Kroll, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  1975-June 1976
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of International Vice President Assistant F.T. Lynch, 1971-1975 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  1971-December 1975
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of International Vice President W.C.Y. McGregor, 1967-1975 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  1967-July 1975
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of International Vice President E.J. Neal, 1970-1976 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  1970-November 1976
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of International Vice President R.O. Norton, 1971-1976 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  1971-March 1976
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of International Vice President J.F. Otero, 1971-1977 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  1971-April 1977
- Grand Lodge Officers - Activities of International Vice President G. Toppen, 1971-1977 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  1971-March 1977
- Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help and Furniture - Rosemont Illinois, 1969-1976 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  1969-May 1976
- Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (W.C.Y. McGregor), 1967-1974 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  1967-May 1974
- Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture, 1974-1979 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  1974-August 1979
- Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (Inventory: Washington Office), 1967-1976 (Box 30, Folder 49)
- Grand Lodge Officers - Monthly Departmental Report, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 50)
  1975-October 1976
- Grand Lodge Officers - Office Supplies, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 51)
- Grand Lodge Officers - Moving Expenses, 1973-1976 (Box 30, Folder 52)
  Replacement of Original File. 1973-August 1976
- Grand Lodge Officers - Bonds of Grand Lodge Officers, 1957-1971 (Box 30, Folder 53)
  July 1957-October 1971
- Grand Lodge Officers - Semi-Monthly Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  October 1975-1976
- Grand Lodge Officers - Departmental Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  December 1976-October 1977
- Weekly Reports of J.C. Fletcher, International Vice President, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  June 1975
- Grand Lodge Officers - Vacations of Officers, Representatives, and Organizers, 1966-1975 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  January 1, 1966-December 1975
- Grand Lodge Officers - Assignments of Organizers, 1972-1976 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  1972-March 1976
- Grand Lodge (General), 1971-1979 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  1971-November 1979
- Grand Lodge (General), 1969 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  December 19, 1969
- Pass Outs of the Executive Council, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  March 29, 1976-April 2, 1976
- Pass Outs Executive Council Meeting, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  September 1976
- Executive Council Meeting, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Pass Outs Executive Council Meeting, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  November 15-16, 1978
- Pass Outs Executive Council Meeting, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  November 12, 1979
- Pass Outs Executive Council Meeting, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  February 1979
- Grand Lodge - Office Supplies, 1972-1979 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Grand Lodge (General), 1974-1979 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  October 1974-December 26, 1979
- Grand Lodge - Data Processing Department, 1973-1978 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  July 1973-October 1978
- Railway Clerks Investment Fund, Incorporated, 1972-1977 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  1972-October 1977
- Auditing and Bonding Department, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  March 1979
- Grand Lodge - Auditing Grand Lodge Accounts, 1974-1979 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  September 1974-October 1979
- Grand Lodge - Liability, Personal Automobile, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  July 1972
- Liability Insurance, Personal Automobiles (Box 32, Folder 10)
  No date.
- Grand Lodge - Union Officials Defense Expense Insurance, 1973-1978 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  November 14, 1973-January 1978
- Grand Lodge - Legal Department, 1974-1979 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  January 1, 1974-November 1979
- Grand Lodge - Labor Educational Department, 1968-1976 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  September 1, 1968-October 26, 1976
- Corporate Priorities Number 4: Report to Leadership Participants, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Grand Lodge - Officers and Employees Group Life Insurance, 1970-1979 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  November 1, 1970-August 1979
- Provident Group Policy R-715: Special Accident Insurance, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  April 1978-September 1979
- Grand Lodge - Group Life Insurance Officers and Employees: American General Life Insurance Company BRAC Policy 5555, 1974-1977 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  June 1974-December 1977
- Grand Lodge - Group Life Insurance Officers and Employees: American General Life Insurance Company BRAC Policy 5555, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  January 1978-December 1979
- Health and Welfare - Florida East Coast Policy GA 23111H, 1971-1976 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  January 1971-March 1976
- Health and Welfare - Travelers Policy GA 23111 J, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  January-August 1973
- Health and Welfare: Koppers Company, Incorporated, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  November 6, 1973
- Travelers Accidental Death and Dismemberment Policy GA-664599, 1976-1979 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  1976-October 1979
- Travelers Special File (C.L. Dennis), 1969 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  January-August 1969
- Grand Lodge - Officers and Employees Group Life Insurance: Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States, 1970-1973 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  May 1, 1970-November 1973. (Assurance=Insurance?)
- Grand Lodge - Group Life Insurance Officers and Employees, 1968-1979 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  June 1968-March 1979
- Grand Lodge - Group Hospital Travelers Policy GA-23111 (Special File - Administrative Department), 1979 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  January 1, 1979-November 1, 1979
- Grand Lodge - Group Hospital Travelers Policy GA-23111 (Special File: Administrative Department), 1976-1978 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  July 1976- December 1978
- Travelers Insurance: Open Enrollment Period, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  April 29, 1974
- Grand Lodge - Group Hospital, Surgical, and Medical Insurance (Airline - Express - Canadian Board of Adjustment), 1971-1979 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  1971-October 1979
- Grand Lodge - Group Hospital, Surgical, and Medical Insurance, 1973-1978 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  June 1973-January 1978
- Grand Lodge - Group Hospital, Surgical, and Medical Insurance Policy GA - 107300, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  February 1978-December 1979
- Grand Lodge - Insurance - Brotherhood of Railway and Airline Clerks Dental and Vision Care Plan, 1974-1979 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  June 19, 1974- July 1979
- Railway Systems and Management Association - Penn-Central Symposium, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  Drake Hotel, Chicago. September 15, 1971. C.L. Dennis.
- Brotherhood of Railway and Airline Clerks - Dental and Visual Care, Provident Policy R-560, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Grand Lodge - Research and Education: Dynamics in Leadership, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Aetna Life and Casualty National Dental Plan - Policy GP-12000, 1975-1979 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  December 1975-December 1979
- Membership Division Breakdown (General), 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  1976-May 1977
- Supreme Court Decisions, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  August 1978
- Correspondence (General), 1976-1979 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  December 1976-December 1979
- Surveys Daniel Yankelovich, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  November 1973-May 1974. Includes Bound Materials.
- Court Decisions, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  January 1, 1974-November 1975
- Association of American Railroads, 1963-1979 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  January 1, 1963-August 1979
- American Association of Railroads - American Sound Transportation Review Organization (ASTRO), 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  June 30, 1970-April 1971
- Brotherhood Building Company - Rentals, 1924-1973 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  1924-March 1973
- Itek Leasing Corporation Lease 1817, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  January 21, 1977
- Board of Directors Building Company - Correspondence regarding meeting, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  January 12, 1978 letter regarding February 10, 1978 meeting.
- Ladies Auxiliary (General), 1922-1972 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  1922-September 1972
- United States Department of Labor (General), 1973-1979 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  June 1973-December 1979
- Department of Labor - Manpower Training Department Administrative Contract, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Proceedings of the National Conference on Railroad-Highway Crossing Safety, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  August 19-22, 1974. Bound.
- United States Department of Labor - Statistics, 1972-1979 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps, 1971-1974 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  1971-May 8, 1974
- Our Cause is People and Other Reports, 1971-1977 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps, 1974-1979 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  May 9, 1974-November 1979
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - National Contract, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  July 1973-November 1974
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - National Contract, 1970-1973 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  1970-June 1973
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Publicity, 1971-1976 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  Includes Newspaper and Bound Materials. 1971-November 1976
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Instructions (Personnel), 1971-1979 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  1971-March 1979
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Personnel, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  January-August 15, 1979
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Travel Authority, 1972-1974 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  February 1972-March 1974
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Moving Costs, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - General Services Administration (GSA) Automobiles, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  1973-September 1974
- United States Department of Labor/Job Corps - Consultants, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- United States Department of Labor/Job Corps - Working Agreements, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  August 1973-February 1974
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Insurance, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  November 5, 1973
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - National Contract Curriculum, 1970-1973 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  1970-December 1973
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - National Contract - Financial Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  1971-December 1972
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - National Contract - Financial Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  January 1973-October 1979
- Department of Labor - National Contract-Reports/General, 1971-1975 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  1971-January 1975
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - National Contract-Reports/Progress, 1971-1974 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  1971-November 1974
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - National Contract-Reports/Financial, 1971-1974 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  1971-February 1974
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - National Contract-Reports/Job Placement, 1971-1974 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Job Support and Follow-up, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  Through October 1979
- Department of Labor - National Contract Reports - Occupational Training Specialist, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  Through November 1979
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - National Contract - Job Placement System, 1971-1974 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  1971-September 1974
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - National Contract - Teacher Training, 1971-1973 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  1971-March 1973
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Centers, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - National Contract Equipment and Furniture Supplies, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - General Services Administration Car, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  November 1967
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - In-Service Training - Field Staff, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  August 1973-October 1974
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Chicago, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Chicago Center/Curriculum, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  Found Empty December 8, 2014.
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Chicago Center/Financial, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Chicago Center/Reports, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Chicago Center/Placement, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Chicago Job Support and Follow-up (Box 36, Folder 18)
  No Date. Found Empty December 8, 2014.
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Los Angeles Center, 1971-1975 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Los Angeles Center/Curriculum, 1971-1973 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Los Angeles Center/Financial, 1971-1972 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Los Angeles Reports, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  Through 1974
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Los Angeles Placement, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Los Angeles Occupational Training Specialists, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Department of Labor - Little Rock Center, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  Through October 1974
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Charleston, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Atlanta, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Atlanta - Financial, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - San Jose Center, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Department of Labor - San Jose Financial, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Department of Labor - Tulsa Center, 1971-1974 (Box 36, Folder 31)
- Department of Labor - Tulsa Center - Financial, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Tulsa Reports, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Department of Labor - Tulsa Center Placement, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Department of Labor - Tulsa Center - Job Support and Follow Up, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Charleston Financial, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Charleston Placement, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Detroit, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Charleston Job Support and Follow-up, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Cleveland, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Department of Labor/Job Corps - Placement, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- United States Department of Labor - Labor Advisory Committee to the Agency for International Development (AID), 1965-1977 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  Formerly International Cooperation Administration. January 1, 1965-May 1977
- United States Department of Labor - Welfare and Pension Plans - Reports, 1964-1975 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  The Bureau of Labor-Management Reports and the Office of Welfare and Pension Plans were Merged on August 121, 1963 into a Single Organization, The Office of Labor-Management and Welfare Pension Reports. September 5, 1964-March 1975
- United States Department of Labor - Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, 1970-1979 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- United States Department of Labor - President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  Replacement of Original File.
- President's Committee for Equal Employment Opportunity, 1965-1970 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  January 1, 1965-1970
- United States Department of Labor - President's National Commission on Productivity, 1973-1978 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- CETA Minneapolis/Saint Paul, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  CETA?
- Strike, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  Includes official strike ballots
- Strikes, 1965-1966 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  January 1, 1965-December 31, 1966
- Strikes, 1968-1970 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  January 1, 1968-December 31, 1970